<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4" modifiedDate="2016-10-15T21:48:58">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Prayer for Peace</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>PRAYER FOR PEACE</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>In the Name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spririt. Amen</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Almighty ever living God, Maker of Heaven and Earth, we thank You for the gift of our beautiful country Kenya.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Thank you for the benefit you have bestowed on each and every Kenyan. Risen Lord, the first gift you shared</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>with your disciples immediately after ressurrection was the gift of peace. They were struck with fear.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Our country is going through a similar experience not knowing who will be killed next.We are praying that You</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>may continue to protect us King of Glory. We condemn the ongoing acts of terrorism in Your Holy Name.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Lord Jesus, we have no intention to take revenge against our enemies because we know and believe that you are</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>always there for and with us.<br/>Let these  enemies of peace not defeat you King of peace. We pray for our political</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>leaders both in Government and in Opposition that as they execute their people given mandate and exercise</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>the democratic right to speak, may they never forget that they are because we are.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>We ask this through Christ our Lord. Amen.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>Our Father..................<br/>Hail Mary....................</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>Glory be to the Father.....<br/>Mary Queen of Peace - pray for us.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
